<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Recipes>
  <Recipe>
    <name>Chocolate Cookie Sandwiches</name>
    <type>Desserts</type>
    <ingredients>4 squares semi-sweet chocolate, 1 1/2 cups granulated sugar, 3 Tbsp or 45ml canola oil, 2 Tbsp or 30 ml milk, 2 tsp or 10 ml of vanilla, 3 eggs, 2 cups all purpose flour,  2 tsp baking powder, 125 gm cream cheese , 1/4 cup or 60 ml non-hydrogenated canola margarine , 1 tsp or 5 ml of vanilla, 2 cups icing sugar</ingredients>
    <method>In a microwave or a heavy saucepan set over low heat, melt chocolate. Then allow it to cool. In a large bowl, combine sugar, canola oil, milk, vanilla, eggs and melted chocolate. Beat well. Sift together flour and baking powder and add to chocolate mixture. Mix well. Cover and chill for 1-2 hours or until dough is easy to handle. Preheat oven to 375 °F (190 °C). Shape dough into 1 inch balls. Place 2 inches. Bake for 10 to 12 minutes or until tops are lightly browned. Remove and cool on wire rack. To prepare filling: In bowl, mix together cream cheese, canola margarine, vanilla and icing sugar. Beat until mixture is smooth and well combined. Place filling in between two cookies.</method>
    <imageurl>http://www.ndtv.com/cooks/images/chocolate-cookie-sandwiches-002_330.jpg</imageurl>
    <date>11/5/2015</date>
  </Recipe>
  <Recipe>
    <name>Molten Chocolate Cake  </name>
    <type>Desserts</type>
    <ingredients>250 ml canola oil, 325g Dark chocolate, 7 eggs, 6 egg yolks, 2/3 cup granulated sugar, 2 Tbsp light brown sugar , 1/2 cup all-purpose flour , 1/2 cup almond flour , 1/4 cup cacao nibs, finely chopped or mini chocolate chips </ingredients>
    <method>In a double boiler, add water to the bottom pot and add canola oil and chocolate to the top pot. Bring water in the bottom pot to a boil. Turn heat to low and stir the oil-chocolate mixture for about 4 minutes,until the chocolate is melted and the mixture is smooth. Make sure the water does not boil again. In a bowl, whisk whole eggs, egg yolks and sugars together until well blended. Whisk the chocolate mixture into the egg mixture until thoroughly incorporated. Add all-purpose flour and almond flour into the chocolate mixture and whisk until just combined. Fold in cacao nibs. Brush 10 small ramekins with canola oil and scoop about 6 Tbsp (90 mL) of cake batter into each ramekin. You may place filled ramekins in refrigerator or freezer for later baking but bring to room temperature before proceeding with the next step. Preheat the oven to 350 °F (180 °C). Bake for 10 minutes. Remove the ramekins from the oven and unmold each of them directly onto a plate. Serve warm with fresh berries and Star Anise- and Orange-Infused Canola Ice Cream.</method>
    <imageurl>http://www.ndtv.com/cooks/images/CIA_._Chocolate_Almond_Molten_Cake_._2014.jpg</imageurl>
    <date>11/5/2015</date>
  </Recipe>
  <Recipe>
    <name>Apple And Walnut Salad</name>
    <type>Breakfast</type>
    <ingredients>3-4 Washington apples, Bowlful of walnuts, 15-20 Basil leaves, Lettuce, 4-5 cups of caster sugar, Black pepper, Curry powder, Balsamic vinegar, Olive oil</ingredients>
    <method>Cut Washington apples into wedges. Heat a pan on low flame, add apples, 2-3 tbsp. balsamic vinegar and 2-3 tbsp. caster sugar. Cook till apples absorb vinegar and sugar, leave aside to cool. Caramelize caster sugar, add walnuts, leave it to cool . Now, in a bowl add 2-3 tbsp. balsamic vinegar and chopped basil leaves. To this, add salt, pepper and olive oil. Whisk and add 1/2 tbsp. curry powder. Finish by crushing caramelized walnuts atop. Serve on a bed of lettuce.
</method>
    <imageurl>http://www.ndtv.com/cooks/images/walnutsalad.jpg</imageurl>
    <date>11/5/2015</date>
  </Recipe>
</Recipes>